{
    "subject": "resource/Joan_Maragall",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Catalonia",
    "human_readable": "Joan Maragall died in Catalonia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9241223335266113,
            "question": "Was Joan Maragall from Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8227450251579285,
            "question": "Where did Joan Maragall die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7229717969894409,
            "question": "When did Joan Maragall die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.582389771938324,
            "question": "Who was Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35639941692352295,
            "question": "What was Joan Maragall's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34507933259010315,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Joan Maragall's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2941790819168091,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2298586070537567,
            "question": "What is Catalonia known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18190956115722656,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1746460497379303,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Catalonia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joan Maragall died in Catalonia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4915_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks in Catalonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4915_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Catalonia known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4915_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Joan Maragall?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4915_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4915_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\nWhile the documents state Joan Maragall was born and lived in Barcelona, Spain (which is in Catalonia), they do not explicitly say he died there.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Joan Maragall was born and raised in Barcelona, Spain, and died on May 4, 1913. Given that Barcelona is a city in Catalonia, the statement \"Joan Maragall died in Catalonia\" can be supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states he was born and raised in Barcelona, Spain.  Additionally, the context mentions his manuscripts are preserved in the Joan Maragall Archive of Barcelona.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}